Inventory of the Francis E. Warren Papers, 1867-1974
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series IV. Early Business Ventures, 1878-1961; 7.6 cubic ft. (21 document boxes) arranged chronologically.
  - Subseries 8. Wyoming Phonograph Company, 1889-1900
    - Legal Documents, Agreements, Memoranda, Correspondence, 1889-1894; microfilm reel 279 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Record Book, 1889-1900; microfilm reel 279 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Notes, Proxy Authorizations, 1895-1900; microfilm reel 279 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 9. Cheyenne Investment Company, 1889-1911
    - Legal Documents, 1889-1894; microfilm reel 279 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Record Book, 1889-1911; contains articles of incorporation, minutes; microfilm reel 279 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of Special Meeting to Deed Property to F. E. W. Proxy Authorizations, Notes, 1898-1910; microfilm reel 279 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 10. Warren Irrigation Company, 1909-1915
    - Certificate of Incorporation, Minutes of Directors Meetings, Bylaws, Newspaper Clipping, 1909; microfilm reel 279 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Journal, 1910; contains articles of organization; microfilm reel 279 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Letterbook, 1910,1915; microfilm reel 279 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 11. Cheyenne Hotels Company, 1910-1946
    - Journal, 1910-1928; microfilm reel 279 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1911-1928; microfilm reel 279 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Hotel Register, 1932-1941; microfilm reel 279 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence & Legal Documents, 1939-1944; microfilm reel 279 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Invoice Book, 1939-1946; contains serial bonds of Cheyenne Hotels Company; microfilm reel 280 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Minute Book, 1910-1939; microfilm reel 280 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Journal, 1929-1943; microfilm reel 280 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Ledger, 1929-1943; microfilm reel 280 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 12. Cheyenne Securities Company, 1910-1961
    - Legal Documents, 1910-1920; microfilm reel 281 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1910-1928; microfilm reel 281 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Journal, 1910-1928; contains articles of organization; microfilm reel 281 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Cash Book, 1928-1939; microfilm reel 281 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Securities Index, 1932-1935; microfilm reel 281 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Financial Records, Balance Sheets, Bond Lists, Inventories, 1954-1958; microfilm reel 281 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Stock Certificate Book, n.d.; microfilm reel 281 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Journal, 1939-1946; microfilm reel 282 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Journal, 1946-1954; microfilm reel 282 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Journal, 1954-1961; microfilm reel 282 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Ledger, 1928-1939; microfilm reel 282 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1939-1946; microfilm reel 282 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Ledger, 1946-1954; microfilm reel 282 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Ledger, 1954-1961; microfilm reel 282 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Invoice Book Containing Serial Bonds, 1939-1947; microfilm reel 282 (Box 212, Folder 1)
- Series V. Mercantile Business Ventures, 1867-1961; 20.25 cubic ft. (73 document boxes).
  Arranged chronologically. Correspondence, legal documents, invoices, receipts, ledgers, journals, cash books, day books and record books.
  - Subseries 1. A. R. Converse, 1867-1875
    - Cash Book, 1867-1868; microfilm reel 283 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Invoice Book, 1867-1868; microfilm reel 283 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Journal, 1867-1868; microfilm reel 283 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Journal, 1867-1871; microfilm reel 283 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Ledger, 1868; microfilm reel 283 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Charge Ledger, 1868-1869; microfilm reel 283 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Cash Book, 1868-1872; microfilm reel 284 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1868-1874; microfilm reel 284 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Cash Book, 1869-1870; microfilm reel 284 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Letterbook, 1869-1871; microfilm reel 284 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Day Book, 1869-1875; microfilm reel 284 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 2. Converse and Warren, 1869-1883
    - Day Book, 1869-1871; microfilm reel 285 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Day Book, 1872-1873; microfilm reel 285 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Day Book, 1873-1874; microfilm reel 285 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Day Book, 1874-1876; microfilm reel 285 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Day Book, 1876; microfilm reel 285 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Letterbook, 1871-1873; microfilm reel 286 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Blotter, 1871-1875; microfilm reel 286 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - Inventory, 1872; microfilm reel 286 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - Cash Book, 1872-1875; microfilm reel 286 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Ledger, 1872-1875; microfilm reel 287 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Letterbook, 1873-1875; microfilm reel 287 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Legal Documents, 1873-1878; microfilm reel 287 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Letterbook, 1875-1876; microfilm reel 287 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Blotter, 1876-1877 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Letterbook, 1877-1878 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Purchase-Sales Journal, 1876-1883 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Valley Ranch Journal, ca. 1884 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3. F. E. Warren Company, 1873-1888
    - Subsubseries 1. Balance Book, 1878-1883
      - Balance Book, 1878-1883 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 2. Cash Books, 1876-1883
      - Cash Book, 1876-1880 (Box 225, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1880-1883 (Box 226, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1880-1881 (Box 227, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1881-1882 (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 3. Day Books, 1877-1884
      - Day Book, 1877-1978 (Box 229, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1878 (Box 230, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1879-1880 (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1880-1881 (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1881-1882 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1882-1883 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1883 (Box 235, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1883-1884 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 4. Ledgers, 1876-1888
      - Ledger, 1876-1880 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1877-1879 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1878-1883 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1880-1883 (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1882-1888 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 4. F. E. Warren Mercantile Company, 1883-1961
    - Subsubseries 1. Business Documents, 1883-1961
      - Legal Documents, 1883-1916 (Box 242, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Proxy Authorizations, Articles of Incorporation, Notes, Certificates, 1883-1949 (Box 242, Folder 2)
      - Memoranda, Receipts, Notes, 1904-1906 (Box 242, Folder 3)
      - Agreement and Correspondence Re: Government Land Purchase, 1910-1913 (Box 242, Folder 4)
      - Property List for F. E. Warren Mercantile Company, 1927 (Box 242, Folder 5)
      - Annual Reports to Secretary of State, 1928-1961 (Box 242, Folder 6)
      - Warranty Deeds, Correspondence, Miscellaneous Legal Documents, 1931-1961 (Box 242, Folder 7)
      - Legal Documents, 1937-1943 (Box 242, Folder 8)
      - Employment Security Commission Quarterly Reports, Determination Notices, Correspondence, Federal Unemployment Tax Returns, Memoranda, 1937-1949 (Box 242, Folder 9)
      - Financial and Tax Documents, 1937-1958 (Box 242, Folder 10)
      - Stock Certificate Book, 1988-1909 (Box 242, Folder 11)
      - Quarterly Tax Returns, 1938-1958 (Box 243, Folder 1)
      - Property Agreements, Correspondence, Releases, Contracts, Certificates, 1944-1961 (Box 243, Folder 2)
      - Employment Security Commission Quarterly Reports, Determination, Notices, Correspondence, Federal Unemployment Tax Returns, Memoranda, 1949-1960 (Box 243, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Contract, 1951-1955 (Box 243, Folder 4)
      - Remodeling Studies for Apartment #1 at 1829 Central for Warren Mercantile Company, 1957 (Box 243, Folder 5)
      - Financial Statement, 1958 (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Subsubseries 2. Cash Books, 1883-1940
      - Cash Book, 1883-1886 (Box 244, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1886-1889 (Box 245, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1889-1892 (Box 246, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1890-1892 (Box 247, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1892-1896 (Box 248, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1896-1902 (Box 249, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1902-1907 (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1907-1917 (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1917-1923 (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1923-1929 (Box 253, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1929-1936 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Cash Book, 1936-1940 (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 3. Day Books, 1884-1902
      - Day Book, 1884-1885 (Box 256, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1885-1886 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1886-1887 (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1887-1889 (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1889-1891 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1891-1895 (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1895-1899 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1899-1901 (Box 263, Folder 1)
      - Day Book, 1901-1902 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 4. Inventory and Invoices, 1884-1924
      - Invoice Book, 1884-1886 (Box 265, Folder 1)
      - F. E. Warren mercantile Co. Inventory, 1901-1924 (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Subsubseries 5. Journals, 1883-1957
      - Journal, 1883-1892 (Box 266, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1892-1903 (Box 267, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1941-1945 (Box 268, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1945-1951 (Box 269, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1951-1957 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 6. Ledgers, 1883-1937
      - Ledger Index (Box 271, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1883-1889 (Box 272, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1888-1900 (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1889-1900 (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1900-1903 (Box 275, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1900-1911 (Box 276, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1901-1913 (Box 277, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1912-1928 (Box 278, Folder 1)
      - Ledger, 1928-1937 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 7. Rent and Record Books, 1883-1961
      - Rent Book, 1915-1922 (Box 280, Folder 1)
      - Record/Minute Book, 1883-1913; Articles of Incorporation (Box 281, Folder 1)
      - Record/Minute Book, 1914-1941 (Box 281, Folder 2)
      - Record Book, 1949-1955 (Box 281, Folder 3)
      - Record Book, 1955-1961 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 8. General Ledgers, 1918-1962
      - General Ledger, 1918-1942 (Box 283, Folder 1)
      - General Ledger, 1941-1951 (Box 284, Folder 1)
      - General Ledger, 1955-1962 (Box 285, Folder 1)
- Series VI. Other Business Material, 1870-1944
  - Subseries 1. Failure of First National Bank of Cheyenne, 1919-1929; 1.2 cubic ft. (3 document boxes)
    Arranged chronologically. Correspondence, legal documents, statements, newspaper and clippings.
    - Reports of Condition of First National Bank of Cheyenne, 1919-1924 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Authorities Notebook-T.E. Mcclintock Receiver of First National Bank of Cheyenne V. Francis E. Warren, 1923 (Box 286, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Clippings, Legal Documents, 1920-1928 (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1923-1926 (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - First National Bank Receiver's Analysis; Hickey Analysis, 1924-1928 (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - Case of Kokrda, Receiver of First National Bank of Cheyenne V. Abbott, Warren, Martin, Sheik, Hewlett and Stock Growers National Bank of Cheyenne, 1924-1928 (Box 287, Folder 4)
      minutes of directors' meetings, correspondence, legaL papers, clippings
    - Case of Kokrda, Receiver of First National Bank of Cheyenne V. Abbott, Warren, Martin Sheik, Hewlett and Stock Growers National Bank of Cheyenne, 1929 (Box 287, Folder 5)
      correspondence
    - Legal Documents, 1925 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, Legal Documents, 1926-1928 (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - First National Bank of Cheyenne Analysis: Perley Morse and Company Report, 1928 (Box 287, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence-Hon. C.W. Bierdick and F. E. Warren, 1923 (Box 288, Folder 1)
      contains some material related to Teapot Dome
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1923-1925 (Box 288, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1923-1926 (Box 288, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence-Otto Gramm, 1923 (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence-P.C. Spencer, 1923-1927 (Box 288, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence-Hon. George E. Abbott and F. E. Warren, 1924 (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - Harry B. Henderson, 1924-1925 (Box 288, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence-B.M. Lyon, 1924-1925 (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence-George B. Mcclellan, 1924 (Box 288, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence-T.E. Mcclintock, 1924-1925 (Box 288, Folder 10)
      Receiver, First National Bank of Cheyenne
    - Correspondence-F.W. Mondell, 1924-1926 (Box 288, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence-S.A. Nelson, 1924 (Box 288, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence-Robert W. Stewart, 1924 (Box 288, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1924 (Box 288, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence-Henry Altman, 1925 (Box 288, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence-Mrs. Frank E. Davis, 1925 (Box 288, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence-Mrs. Mary E. Edwards, 1925 (Box 288, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence-Albert D. Walton, 1925 (Box 288, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence-John B. Kendrick, 1925 (Box 288, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence-Fred Warren, 1927 (Box 288, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence-L.M. Wells, 1927 (Box 288, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 2. Miscellaneous Business Papers and Correspondence, 1878-1944; 1.5 cubic ft. (4 document boxes).
    Arranged chronologically. Correspondence, legal documents, maps, sketches, newspaper clippings and statements. This series is divided into 2 subseries:
    - Subsubseries 1. Miscellaneous Business Papers, 1878-1944
      - Leases, 1878-1879 (Box 289, Folder 1)
      - Inventory of Tools Belonging to D. D. Mining Company, 1880 (Box 289, Folder 2)
      - Trial Balance Book: Various Enterprises, 1882-1886 (Box 289, Folder 3)
      - Capitol Building Bond and Capitol Building Bond Board Minute Book, 1886 (Box 289, Folder 4)
      - Certificate from Cheyenne Board of Trade, 1888 (Box 289, Folder 5)
      - Barn Outfit Inventory, 1889 (Box 289, Folder 6)
      - F. E. Warren Statement Book: Various Enterprises, 1892-1907 (Box 289, Folder 7)
      - Crow Creek Ranch Ledger, 1893-1894 (Box 289, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence-Re: Various Enterprises, 1896 (Box 289, Folder 9)
      - F. E. Warren Inventory: Bills Receivable, Notes, Real Estate, Chattels, Furniture, Bonds, Stocks, Inclusive of all Business Enterprises and Personal Property, 1907 (Box 289, Folder 10)
      - Belvoir Ranch Inventory, 1907 (Box 289, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence-Re: Land Sales and Agricultural Enterprises, 1913 (Box 289, Folder 12)
      - Tax Information for Various Companies, 1921-1927 (Box 289, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous Land Purchases and Sales, 1927-1929 (Box 289, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, ca.1928-1944 (Box 289, Folder 15)
      - Newspaper Clippings-Re: Warren Apartments, 1937 (Box 289, Folder 16)
      - Wyoming, Sheridan and Cheyenne Maps and Sketches for Permits to Lay Drains (Box 289, Folder 17)
      - Ledger, 1937-1940; consolidation of debits and credits (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - Subsubseries 2. Correspondence with Hiram Sapp and Others, 1884-1929
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1884-1929 (Box 291, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence with H. Sapp and Others, 1896-1901 (Box 291, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence with H. Sapp and Others, 1902-1916 (Box 291, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence with H. Sapp and Others, 1907-1910 (Box 291, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence with H. Sapp and Others, 1910-1914 (Box 291, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence with H. Sapp and Others, 1915-1919 (Box 292, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence with H. Sapp and Others, 1920-1926 (Box 292, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence With Hiram Sapp and Others, 1927,1929 (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3. Legal Documents, 1870-1918; 1.85 cubic ft. (3 document boxes).
    Arranged chronologically according to document's filing date. Quit claim deeds, warranty deeds, mortgages, releases, bills of sale, leases, liens, abstracts of title, proofs of labor, stock brands, deeds of trust, mining notices of location, affidavits, homestead certificates, foreclosure deeds, bonds, and chattel mortgages.
    - Legal Documents-Uprr, 1870-1897 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Legal Documents, 1875-1907 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Quit Claim Deeds, 1875-1908 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Sheep Papers, 1877-1886 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Warranty Deeds, 1877-1902 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Mortgages, 1877-1907 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Releases Of Mortgages, 1877-1907 (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - Warranty Mortgage Deeds, 1875,1878-1879 (Box 293, Folder 8)
    - Cattle Papers, 1878,1883 (Box 293, Folder 9)
    - Bills of Sale, 1878-1900 (Box 293, Folder 10)
    - Chattel Mortgages, 1879-1900 (Box 293, Folder 11)
    - Warranty Deeds, 1879-1909 (Box 293, Folder 12)
    - Deeds, 1880-1898 (Box 293, Folder 13)
    - Western Union Telegraph Co., 1881-1882 (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Liens, 1881-1898 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Abstracts of Title, 1881-1903 (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Proof of Labor, 1882-1898 (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - Stock Brands, 1882-1900 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Releases of Deeds of Trust, 1883-1897 (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - Wyoming Meat Co., 1883-1898 (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Mining-Notices of Location, 1883-1904 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Legal Documents, 1884-1911 (Box 294, Folder 9)
    - Water Rights and Irrigation Ditches, 1885-1897 (Box 294, Folder 10)
    - Trustees of First Baptist Church of Laramie, 1886 (Box 294, Folder 11)
    - Affidavits, 1886-1912 (Box 294, Folder 12)
    - Cheyenne and Burlington Railroad Company, 1887 (Box 294, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Legal Documents, 1887-1898 (Box 294, Folder 14)
    - Trust Deeds, 1888-1893 (Box 294, Folder 15)
    - Renewal Affidavits for Chattel Mortgages, 1888-1904 (Box 294, Folder 16)
    - Mining Documents, 1889-1897 (Box 294, Folder 17)
    - Homestead Certificates, 1889-1912 (Box 294, Folder 18)
    - Treasurer's Deed, 1890 (Box 294, Folder 19)
    - Cemetery Lot Certificates, 1890-1891 (Box 294, Folder 20)
    - Lease, 1891 (Box 294, Folder 21)
    - Certificates of Appropriation, 1892 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - I.O.O.F. Albany Lodge #7-Bonds, 1891-1892 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Notice of Estray, 1892,1895 (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Chattel Mortgages, 1892-1896 (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Wyoming Investment Company, 1893 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - Chattel Mortgages, 1893-1895 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Chattel Mortgages, 1895-1900 (Box 295, Folder 7)
    - The W. H. Holliday Co., 1897-1900 (Box 295, Folder 8)
    - Pacific Investment Co., 1898 (Box 295, Folder 9)
    - Foreclosure Deeds, 1901 (Box 295, Folder 10)
    - Rocky Mountain Bell Telephone Company, 1906 (Box 295, Folder 11)
    - School Section Leasing, 1906 (Box 295, Folder 12)
    - Cheyenne Realty Co., 1915-1918 (Box 295, Folder 13)
    - School Land Leases, 1904-1906 (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - School Land Leases, 1907 (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - School Land Leases, 1909-1910 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - School Land Leases, 1911 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - School Land Leases, 1911 (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - School Land Leases, 1912-1917 (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - Addendum: Oversized Material 1874-1909, 1971 and Artifacts
      - Cheyenne Maps, 1887-1901; (Subgroup III) (Box 297, Folder 1)
      - Cheyenne Fort Russell Water Supply W.L.S. 1,2,3, ca.1909; (Subgroup III) (Box 297, Folder 2)
      - Maps: Manilla 1899, Mount Warren Silver Crown Mining District, 1897-1899; (Subgroup II) (Box 297, Folder 3)
      - Frances E. Warren Political, 1874-1900; (Subgroup I) (Box 297, Folder 4)
      - Warren Live Stock Co.-Land, Fencing, 1906; (Subgroup III) (Box 297, Folder 5)
      - Photograph of General John J. Pershing, 1922; autographed (Box 297, Folder 6)
      - Plaque, 1971; University of Wyoming Cowboy Joe club to Francis E. Warren (Box 298)
      - Rubber Stamp-F.E. Warren, n.d. (Box 298)
      - Metal Stamp-F.E. Warren, n.d. (Box 298)
      - Metal Signature Bar-Francis E. Warren, n.d. (Box 298)
      - Plat Map Showing F. E. Warren's Cheyenne Real Estate Holdings, 1901 (Box 299)
    - Second Addendum: Papers and artifacts and oversize, 1885-1929
      - Biographies, n.d. (Box 300, Folder 1)
      - Cheyenne Opera House Programs, 1900-1903 (Box 300, Folder 2)
      - Congressional Delegation Visit to Alaska, 1923 (Box 300, Folder 3)
      - Congressional Delegation Visit to Hawaii, 1915 (Box 300, Folder 4)
      - Congressional Delegation Visit to the National Parks, 1923 (Box 300, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1885-1925 (Box 300, Folder 6)
      - Fort D.A. Russell Visit, 1929 (Box 300, Folder 7)
      - Journal of Trip Through Wyoming, Sept. 1911 (Box 300, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1910, 1929 (Box 300, Folder 9)
      - Newsclippings, 1890-1929 (Box 300, Folder 10)
      - Photographs -- Crystal Lake and Granite Springs Reservoirs (Box 300, Folder 11)
      - Photographs -- Miscellaneous, 1870-1912 (Box 300, Folder 12-13)
      - Photographs -- Sheep Shearing, n.d. (Box 300, Folder 14)
      - Photographs -- Warren Family, 1916 (Box 301, Folder 1)
      - Photographs -- Warren Livestock Company, n.d. (Box 301, Folder 2)
      - Political Cartoons, n.d. (Box 301, Folder 3)
      - Speeches, n.d. (Box 301, Folder 4)
      - Stock certificate book - Cheyenne Hotel Co., 1910-1942 (Box 301, Folder 5)
      - Wyoming volunteers - Spanish American War, 1898-1902 (Box 301, Folder 6)
      - Oversized Photograph of Francis E. Warren, n.d. (Oversized envelope, Folder 1)
      - One Pair of Women's Long White Evening Gloves., n.d. (Box Artifacts)
    - Safe Material has been photocopied and copies returned to the appropriate place in the collection, 1864-1929
      - Cleveland, Grover, 1886; Letter (Box Safe, Folder 1)
      - Coolidge, Calvin, 1920-1928; letters (Folder 2)
      - Garfield, James Rudolph, 1909; letter (Folder 3)
      - Harding, Warren G., 1920-1923; letters (Folder 4)
      - Hoover, Herbert, 1928,1929; letters (Folder 5)
      - Kendrick, John B., 1925; letter (Folder 6)
      - Mckinley, William, 1900; letters (Folder 7)
      - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1901-1907; letters (Folder 8)
      - Taft, William Howard, 1905-1912; letters (Folder 9)
      - Wilson, Woodrow, 1917,1919; letters (Folder 10)
      - Confederate $10 Bill, 1864 (Folder 10)
      - Dinner Invitation, 1917 (Box 11)
- Transcripts
  - Typed transcripts of correspondence. business records, and other materials from the F.E. Warren papers (Box 325)
- Additional Container Lists
  The American Heritage Center is in the process of converting its older container lists to a more accessible format. This link is to an older version of a container list.
  - Link to Accessioning Worksheet (PDF)